Delicious!
Fluffy!
Here comes the ramen!
Sano Ramen
Mellow
Gentle taste
Everyone
Wow!
The carrion shark alone is about 50 times more exciting!
Delicious!
I'm in the ramen club so I'll eat it as many times as I can
It's low and cute!
Thank you for the food!
I'm going to enjoy eating Sano ramen and picking up souvenirs at this service area all day today!
And this is Sanomaru-kun!
He seems to be a character named SANOMARU-kun, and he's cute!
What is this thing with ramen on its head?
I was a little curious about this.
I'm really curious about this... Sauce cutlet!
Is it a cutlet?
But chopsticks?
No, definitely not chopsticks.
I was thinking maybe ramen chopsticks.
I'm sure there's probably someone in there with the right answer.
We'll see later.
Okay, I'm going to go now.
I'll see you later.
I'm off!
Here it is, the ramen!
Have you ever had Sano ramen?
Well, I've only had it in a cup.
With vegetables and other options.
I've never had a complete Sano ramen before.
I've never had spinach in it.
And I love green onions, so I was happy to see more green onions.
Have you ever had it before?
No, not at all. It's my first time.
Then I want to try it for the first time. Let's eat. Then I want to eat for the first time. Let's eat.
Let's eat.
Ready, go!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Soy sauce base? Soy sauce base?
It's so refreshing!
The noodles are also very sticky and delicious!
I love this type of noodle so much!
It's so delicious!
I have a tendency to get sick to my stomach
I'm grateful for the lightness of the noodles.
It's so delicious!
Yes, Mr. Holaiken!
Yes, just now.
It's fast!
Quick hassle.
Driving from the SANO service area just now
Here we are at Mr. Holaiken!
Mr. Horaiken, quite an original!
The original SANO Ramen?
Close to the original!
SANO Ramen is very close to the original SANO Ramen.
There are a lot of autographs and so on.
In '93?
We weren't born yet.
We were not born yet.
I'm so happy to be here.
I'm going to have my second drink now.
I'm going to eat.
We're a ramen club.
I'll eat as many as I can!
Yes, that's why I'm here.
Amazing!
It's a little bit too much!
It's a lot of ramen!
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit! Bon appétit!
Want some first?
Eat first.
Okay, I'll go.
Mmm.
What's with the top? It's a pretty solid surface.
Me.
A part.
How is it delicious?
Boo-boo. Sushi flavor.
Delicious, delicious, delicious!
Yes, that's why I ate ramen!
I finished it and had a second bowl of ramen!
I finished it and had a second bowl too!
I did my best as a ramen club!
It was so delicious!
We drove around all day today. How was it?
Every restaurant had a different flavor.
Both ramen restaurants were so delicious that I could eat them all in one sitting!
The ramen was from the same car.
It was ramen from the same car, but it was totally different at each restaurant.
I wanted to do the same thing again.
I want to do the same thing again!
I'd be happy if I could go on a ramen tour!
By the way, you can read an article about this in Highway Walker.
Highway Walker wrote an article about it.
I hope you will check it out!
And I'd be happy if you could follow me on Highway Walker
I hope you will follow the official X page of Highway Walker.
Thank you very much!
Good night.
I went to Shiraiso Falls for Highway Walker's interview!
It's so clear and amazing!
You can see it!
It's amazing!
It's kind of low and pretty.
It's great to feel the nature!
After that, grilled Iwana? After this, I will go to Iwana's salt baked?
I'm going to eat grilled salt and kamameshi of the pass together!
Looking forward to it!
I am looking forward to it!
Bon appétit!
Yes, we got Iwana's little medicine!
You did it!
That's great!
I heard that you can eat everything in the morning, so I'm a little curious.
Tummy!
stomach
Tummy.
Mmm! Delicious!
Fluffy!
Delicious!
I'm already thankful that it's packed with so much meat.
I can't wait to try it again!
anterior Ar mistaken
No problem.
I just came back from visiting Shiraito Falls.
Yokogawa Service Area
I came here!
The kamameshi (rice cooked in a pot) is
Amazing!
It seems to be a specialty of the area.
Okinoya's “Touge no Kamameshi”!
It's warm, isn't it?
It's very heavy.
Shall we open it?
Let's open it right away!
Wow!
It's so cute!
Cute wood on the side.
It's got writing on it.
Here we go!
Seino.
Wow!
Wow! Wow!!!
Looks delicious!
It smells so good!
Smells so good!
Looks so good!
There's so many ingredients in here.
So many ingredients.
A monk?
Monk and...
Chicken?
Chicken and...
Chestnuts?
And in the middle, there's a quail.
Quail in the middle.
Shiitake mushrooms.
What is she?
Anzu.
Anzu!
And bamboo shoots.
There are a lot of bamboo shoots!
Delicious!
full of colors
Delicious inside!
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Which one shall I eat first?
Which shall I eat first?
I'll start with the meat.
Let's start with the meat.
Mmm!
Wait, it's soaked up all the flavor.
Delicious.
Delicious!
I'm kind of curious about the rice, too.
Yum!
Delicious! Delicious!
The rice soaked up so much flavor!
Wow!
It's so good!
Take care of the rice, too.
Mmm!
It's soaked in flavor.
The goodness of the kamadoki.
It's so cute!
I was curious about this apricot.
I don't see this kind of water very often.
Delicious!
I think this is the first apricot tambing I've ever had.
Sweet?
Slightly sweet.
But it's warm, so it goes really well with rice.
It's true, it goes well with rice.
It's delicious.
What do you think of kamameshi? Have you ever had it before?
Have you ever had it in a pot this big?
When I was very young.
That's exactly what I had here at Touge no Kamameshi.
I think I've been here before.
It's like I told my parents I went here a long time ago.
It's so nice!
You can eat in a train car like this.
Just eating in the train is 50 times more exciting!
Delicious!
Did I mention that I'm really tired?
I did say that once.
Wow, it's really great!
It's just too good to be served in a vehicle that's being used.
I'm going to have it again in the future.
So today we had the day's dinner, and it was so delicious!
I had so much fun eating all the delicious food today!
I'm so happy and full of happiness that I got to eat a lot of delicious food today, and I was able to feel the nature a little further away. I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
And today... we were able to sit down at the Auster... and we had a long-awaited meeting... and I've been wanting to say goodbye... and I've been longing to say goodbye... and I've been wanting to say goodbye to the Auster.
I've always wanted to meet him... and he's got such a cute little face.
We've become friends... we've become friends... and I'm so glad we got to ride in such a nice car... and see all these amazing places... and have fun...
I'm glad we got to ride in such a nice car and see all these great spots.
Well, that's all for now, I'm on my way.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.